Guide to the Montana Department of Environmental Quality, Director's Office records 1908-2002
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - Board of Health, Meetings, September 1950-July 1959 (Box-folder 9)
  - Gallatin County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Gallatin County, Beaver Creek subdivision, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Gallatin County, Big Sky Development, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - Gallatin County, Big Western Pine Motel (W. Yellowstone), 1974 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Gallatin County, Bozeman Problem Drinking Center, 1973 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Gallatin County, Bridger Pine subdivision, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Gallatin County, Comprehensive Health Planning Council, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Gallatin County, Cougar Park subdivision, 1974 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Gallatin County, Madison Hotel (W. Yellowstone), 1974 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Gallatin County, Parkview subdivision, 1974 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Gallatin County, Springhill subdivision, 1975 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Gallatin County, Weather modification, 1972 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Garfield County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Glacier County (Auto-wrecking facilities), 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Golden Valley County, 1973 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Granite County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Hill County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Hill County, Alcoholism, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Hill County, Family Planning Program, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Hill County, Havre sewage/Milk River hearing Transcript (Sugar Factory at Chinook), 1938 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Jefferson County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Jefferson County, Boulder River School and Hospital, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Jefferson County, Diamond S Ranchotel Swimming Pool (Boulder), 1972-1975 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Judith Basin County (Sapphire Village), 1972-1976 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Lake County, 1960-1976 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Lake County, Flathead Reservation Alcoholism Program, 1974 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - Lewis and Clark County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Lewis and Clark County, Children and Youth Project Plan, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 10/28-30)
  - Lewis and Clark County, Anaconda and East Helena, “Contract on Chemistry of Precipitation”, 1973 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - Lewis and Clark County, E. Helena Study, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Lewis and Clark County, E. Helena Wastewater Treatment Lagoon, 1975 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Lewis and Clark County, Family Planning Program, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 10/34)
  - Lewis and Clark County, Placer Hotel, 1972 (Box-folder 10/35)
  - Lewis and Clark County, “Southwestern Montana Areawide Alcohol – Drug Grants”, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 10/36)
  - Lewis and Clark County, St. John’s/St. Peters Hospital, 1973 (Box-folder 10/37)
  - Lewis and Clark County, “Stroke Rehab (Aging)”, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 10/38)
  - Lewis and Clark County, Youth Development Program/Bureau, 1973 (Box-folder 10/39)
  - Liberty County – McCone County, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 11/1-4)
  - McCone County, McCone County Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Meagher County – Missoula County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/6-10)
  - Missoula County, Air Pollution Grant, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Missoula County, Alcoholism, 1973 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Missoula County, Child Development Center, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Missoula County, Community Hospital, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Missoula County, CHP Rural Health Care Project and Site Survey (University of Montana), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/15-16)
  - Missoula County, Drug Abuse Project, 1972 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Missoula County, Family Planning Services Project, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Missoula County, Flor-Haven Home, 1974 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Missoula County, “Gals Against Smog and Pollution” (GASP), 1970 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Missoula County, Health Maintenance Organization, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Missoula County, Lincoln Hills subdivision, 1976 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Missoula County, Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Missoula County, Missoula Rehab Center, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 11/24)
  - Missoula County, Northwestern Areawide Health Planning Council, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 11/25)
  - Missoula County, Palace Hotel, 1972 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - Missoula County, Priess Hotel, 1972 (Box-folder 11/27)
  - Missoula County, Seeley Lake Project, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/28)
  - Missoula County, Urban Planning Research and Demo. Project, 1972 (Box-folder 11/29)
  - Missoula County, Vista Project, 1972 (Box-folder 11/30)
  - Missoula County, Western Montana Fish and Game Association (Hoerner-Waldorf), 1973 (Box-folder 11/31)
  - Musselshell County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/32)
  - Park County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/33)
  - Park County, Chase Boarding Home (Livingston), 1974 (Box-folder 11/34)
  - Park County, Frontier Retirement Home (Livingston), 1974-1976 (Box-folder 11/35)
  - Park County, Mint Apartments, 1974 (Box-folder 11/36)
  - Park County, Petit’s Inn and Range Rider Lodge, 1974 (Box-folder 11/37)
  - Phillips County – Richland County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 11/38-45)
  - Richland County, 1975 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Richland County: Economic Development Association of Eastern Montana, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Roosevelt County (Mental Health Services), 1966 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Roosevelt County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Roosevelt County: Eastern Montana Community Health Association, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 12/5-6)
  - Roosevelt County: Nurses Bargaining (Trinity Hospital), 1971 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Rosebud County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Rosebud County: Colstrip First Aid Facilities, 1974 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Sheridan County – Sanders County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 12/10-11)
  - Sanders County: Clark Fork Valley Hospital, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Silver Bow County, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Silver Bow County: Butte Family Service Center and Maternal and Child Health, 1976 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Silver Bow County: Comprehensive Health Planning Program, 1973 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Silver Bow County: Family Planning, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Silver Bow County: Group Practice Program, 1971 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Silver Bow County: Southwestern Areawide Health Planning Council, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Silver Bow/Lewis and Clark County: Survey of Subdivisions, 1973 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Stillwater County – Valley County, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 12/20-25)
  - Valley County: Glasgow Air force Base, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Wheatland County – Yellowstone County, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 12/27-30)
  - Yellowstone County: Air Pollution, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Yellowstone County: Cardiology Review (Billings), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - Yellowstone County: Family Planning, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - Yellowstone County: Gage Hotel hearing, 1972 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Yellowstone County: Indian Health Contracts, 1953-1962 (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Yellowstone County: Memorial Society of Montana, 1972 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Yellowstone County: “Mental Retardation Project”, 1967 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Yellowstone County: Northern Rockies Regional Cancer Treatment Center, 1973 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Yellowstone County: “Possible Health Dept.”, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Yellowstone County: St. Vincent’s Hospital Intensive Care Nursery, 1971 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Yellowstone County: “Socioeconomic Findings, Environmental Health Conditions and Health Statistics, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Yellowstone County: Southcentral Comprehensive Health Planning, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Bylaws, Montana Health Planning Council, undated (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Committee for Statewide Planning for Vocational Rehabilitation Services, 1968 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Council on Natural Resources, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13/10-12)
  - Interim Committee on Science and Technology, 1969 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Nursing Home Administrator’s Licensing Board, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Pacific Northwest River Basin Committee (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Rocky Mountain Development Council, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Rural Development Program, 1962, 1970 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Water Pollution Control, 1964-1971 (Box-folder 13/18-20)
  - Regional Health Director, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 13/21-22)
  - Regional (Denver): Public Health Services Act, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Regional (Denver): Denver Meeting, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 13/24)
  - Regional (Denver): Public Health Services, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Regional (Denver): Bureau of Health Insurance Automatic Sprinklers, 1971 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Regional (Denver): Children’s Bureau, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Regional (Denver): Civil Defense, 1962 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Regional (Denver): Civil Rights, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Regional (Denver): Denver Meetings, 1972 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Regional (Denver): Environmental Protection Agency, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Regional (Denver): Health Insurance, 1968 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Regional (Denver): Housing and Urban Development, 1972 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Regional (Denver): Health Care Facilities, 1970, 1973 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Regional (Denver): Hospital Construction, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Regional (Denver): Medicare, 1969 (Box-folder 14/11)
  - Regional (Denver): Maternal and Child Health, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Regional (Denver): Public Health Services, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Regional (Denver): Radiological Health, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Regional (Denver): Scarcity Areas, 1972 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Regional (Denver): Social and Rehabilitation, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Regional (Denver): “V.D.” (Venereal Disease), 1969 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Regional (San Francisco): Health Advisory Committee, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - State Board of Health, Contract (Deaconess Hospital), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - National: “Ad Hoc Consultant Group, HSMHA-ASTHO, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - National: Institute of Health, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - National: Budget and Management, 1973 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - National: Miscellaneous, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 14/23)
  - National: Office of Economic Opportunity, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 14/24)
  - National: ABM Area Project, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - National: Communicable Disease Center (Atlanta), 1968-1973 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - National: Comprehensive Health Planning, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - National: Environmental Protection Agency, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - National: Federal Comprehensive Health Planning, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - National: Federal Trade Commission, 1969 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - National: Food and Drug Administration, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 15/7-8)
  - National: Health Insurance Meetings, 1969 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - National: Health Services and Mental Health Admin, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - National: Hill-Burton (Health Care Facility Service), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - National: Indian Health Service, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - National: Institute of Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - National: Institute of Health, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - National: Institutional Assurance on Human Subjects, 1967 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - National: Miscellaneous (Microbiology Lab Div. Review), 1968, 1970 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - National: “Miscellaneous Federal Agencies”, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - National: National Weather Service, 1971 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - National: Refuse Act 1899 (Rivers and Harbors Act), 1971 (Box-folder 15/19)
  - National: Research Grants Program, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 15/20)
  - National: Social and Rehabilitation Service, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 15/21)
  - National: Social Security Administration, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 15/22)
  - National: U.S. Department of the Interior, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 15/23)
  - National: U.S. Forest Service, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 15/24)
  - National: U.S. Public Health Service (USPHS), 1968-1970 (Box-folder 15/25-27)
  - Regional (Denver): Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism Prevention, Treatment, and Rehabilitation, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 15/28)
  - Regional (Denver): Air Pollution Grant, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 15/29-30)
  - Regional (Denver): Beauty Culturists Board, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 15/31)
  - Regional (Denver): Cooperative Areawide Health Planning, 1973 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Regional (Denver): Cleft Palate Program, 1958-1973 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Regional (Denver): Dental Prevention, “The State Of the Art”, 1973 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Regional (Denver): Dental Health Grant, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Regional (Denver): “Education for Action: Organizing County Health Planning Units, 1973 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Regional (Denver): Epidemiology, 1968 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Regional (Denver): Emergency Health Services, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Regional (Denver): Emergency Care Program, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Regional (Denver): Food and Drug Labeling Survey, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Regional (Denver): “FDA Survey of Interstate Highway Interchanges Food Service Facilities, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Regional (Denver): CHP “Health Care Delivery System Development, 1973 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Regional (Denver): Health Mobilization, 1963, 1968 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Regional (Denver): Hearing Conservation Program, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Regional (Denver): Statewide Family Planning, 1973 (Box-folder 16/14-15)
  - Hill-Burton Construction, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 16/16)
  - “Mental Retardation Planning Grant”, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 16/17)
  - “Mental Retardation Project”, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Migrant Health Grant, 1973 (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Migrant Health Program, Yellowstone Co., 1965-1972 (Box-folder 16/20)
  - “Montana Health Referral Service for Medical Rejectees”, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 16/21)
  - “Montana Indians and Health – A Cultural Awareness Conference”, 1973 (Box-folder 16/22)
  - National Clearinghouse for Poison Control Center, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 16/23)
  - Neurological and Sensory Disease Project, 1962 (Box-folder 16/24)
  - Occupational Alcoholism Program, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 16/25)
  - Occupational Health, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 16/26)
  - Oral Cancer Detection Study, 1964 (Box-folder 16/27)
  - Pesticides, Pesticide Demonstration Program (1972 Annual Report), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 16/28-30)
  - Rubella Immunization Project, 1969 (Box-folder 16/31)
  - Solid Waste Disposal Grant and Program, 1966-1971, 1973 (Box-folder 16/32-33)
  - Short-term Training for Nurses, 1967 (Box-folder 16/34)
  - Smoking and Health Project, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 16/35)
  - Training, 1966-1974 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Tuberculosis Control Project, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Tuberculosis Control Project Grant, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Vaccination Assistance Project Grant, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Vaccination, Public Health Services, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Venereal Disease Grant (includes “Today’s VD Control Problem” reports, 1970, 1973), 1957-1973 (Box-folder 17/6-8)
  - Water Pollution Control Grant Program, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Water Pollution Control, Portland, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Water Quality Control, Colorado River Basin, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Water Quality Control, Clarks Fork River Basin, 1970 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Water Quality Control, Missouri River Basin, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - WIC (Women, Infants and Children) Program, 1973 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - American Academy of Pediatrics, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - American Association of Public Health Physicians, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - American Public Health Association, 1974 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - American Public Health Association, “Continuing Education”, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - American Public Health Association, Position Papers and Meetings, 1968 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - American Social Health Association, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Association of State Maternal and Child Health and Crippled Children Directors, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Bureau of Narcotics, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - Council of State Governments, Health Field Licensing Questionnaire, 1969 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - EPA, Denver, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Epilepsy, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Montana Association for Mental Health, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Montana Commission for Nursing and Nursing Ed., 1972 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Montana Hospital Association, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Montana Inter-tribal Policy Board, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Montana Lung Association, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Montana Medical Association (MMA), 1967-1973 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - MMA, Carpeting in Hospitals study, 1968 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - MMA, Committee on Public Health and Well- being, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - MMA, Executive Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - MMA, Foundation for Medical Care Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - MMA, Maternal and Child Welfare Committee (Includes Abortion policy for Montana), 1973 (Box-folder 18/17)
  - MMA, Meetings (Annual and Interim) (Box-folder 18/18-19)
  - MMA, Cancer Committee (Includes Tumor registry), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/20)
  - MMA, Montana Physician’s Union, 1973 (Box-folder 18/21)
  - MMA, Montana Nutrition Project, 1974 (Box-folder 18/22)
  - MMA, Montana Planned Parenthood, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Montana National Society for Crippled Children and Adults, 1965, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Montana Nurses Association, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Montana Nursing Home Association, 1974 (Box-folder 18/26)
  - Montana Public Health Association, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Montana State Low-Income Organization, 1973 (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Montana Wildlife Federation, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Montana, Interim Committee on Science and Technology, 1970 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Montana, “Kidney Dialysis”, 1971 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Montana, Legislation, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Montana, Medical Facilities Utilization Review, 1971 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Montana, “Miscellaneous Diseases”, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Montana, Miscellaneous (in-state), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Montana, Miscellaneous (out-of-state), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Montana, Neonatal Intensive Care Unit, 1971 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Montana, “Other State Health Departments”, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Montana, “Rabies”, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Montana, Schools of Public Health, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Montana, Selective Service, 1972 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - Montana, “State College School of Nursing Public Health Agreement”, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - National Health Council, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/15)
  - National Safety Council, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 19/16)
  - National, Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education (WICHE) (Regional Medical Program), 1968-1973 (Box-folder 19/17)
  - Tumor Registry (Montana), 1968-1971 (Box-folder 19/18)
  - U.S. Congress, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/19-20)
  - Beaverhead County – Cascade County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 19/21-23)
  - Cascade County, Acid Waste Mines, 1971 (Box-folder 19/24)
  - Cascade County, Air Pollution Grants, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 19/25)
  - Cascade County, Belt Creek Sewage Problem, 1974 (Box-folder 19/26)
  - Cascade County, Board of Trade Hotel, 1972 (Box-folder 19/27)
  - Cascade County, Columbus Hospital, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 19/28)
  - Cascade County, Deaconess Hospital, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 19/29)
  - Cascade County, Family Planning (Great Falls), 1973-1976 (Box-folder 19/30)
  - Cascade County, Great Falls site visit, 1973 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Cascade County, Information and Referral Center, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Cascade County, Poucher’s Place Hotel (Neihart), 1973 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Cascade County, “Providence Resocialization Service (Alcoholism)”, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Cascade County, Rainbow Hotel (Great Falls), 1972 (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Cascade County, Sun Prairie subdivision (Great Falls), 1976 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Choteau County – Fergus County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 20/7-10)
  - Flathead County, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Flathead County, Canyon Hotel, 1972 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Flathead County, Flathead Lake, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Flathead County, “Kalispell-Alcoholism”, 1974 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Flathead County, Mission Valley Family Planning, 1972 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Attorney General (Opinions), 1908-1972 (Box-folder 20/16-17)
  - Civil Defense Agency (Box-folder 20/18)
  - Department of Administration, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 20/19-20)
  - Environmental Quality Council, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 20/21)
  - Governor’s Office, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 20/22-23)
  - Governor’s Office, AVCO Economic Systems, 1969-172 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Governor’s Office, Budget and Program Planning, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Governor’s Office, Federal State Coordinator, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Governor’s Office, “Governor’s Committee to Study Needs of C.P. Center, Billings”, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Governor’s Office, “Keep Montana Beautiful” Committee, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Governor’s Office, Legislative Proposals, 1974 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Governor’s Office, Miscellaneous, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Governor’s Office, “Multi-county Districting”, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 21/8)
  - Human Resources, Human Services Project, 1974 (Box-folder 21/9)
  - Legislation, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 21/10)
  - “Miscellaneous State Agencies”, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/11)
  - Personnel, Collective Bargaining, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 21/12)
  - “CODE – Prostitution” (Instances of prostitution In Great Falls, Black Eagle, Butte, Helena, Missoula, Libby and Troy), 1955-1959 (Box-folder 21/13)
  - State Board of Health Building, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 21/14)
  - Departmental Reorganization (1971), 1969-1973 (Box-folder 21/15-18)
  - Department of Institutions, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 21/19)
  - Department of Planning and Economic Development, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 21/20)
  - Department of Planning and Economic Development, “Task Force on Environmental Impact of Coal Dev.”, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 21/21)
  - Department of Public Instruction, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 21/22)
  - Commission on Aging, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 22/1)
  - “Crow Project Meeting” (Construction of jail, Detox center, rehab center, and pool on Crow Agency), 1970 (Box-folder 22/2)
  - Department of Public Welfare, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 22/3)
  - “Federal State Meeting”, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 22/4)
  - Fish and Game, 1959-1972 (Box-folder 22/5)
  - Human Resources, 1969 (Box-folder 22/6)
  - Human Resources, Montana Council on HR, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 22/7)
  - Human Resources, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box-folder 22/8)
  - Law Enforcement and Public Safety, 1969 (Box-folder 22/9)
  - Law Enforcement and Public Safety, Highway Patrol, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 22/10-11)
  - Law Enforcement and Public Safety, Crime Control Commission, 1970 (Box-folder 22/12)
  - Law Enforcement and Public Safety, Highway Safety Committee (Box-folder 22/13)
  - Montana Legislative Committee, 1965-1970 (Box-folder 22/14-15)
  - Natural Resources and Development, Council on Natural Resources and Development, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 22/16-17)
  - State Government Officials, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 22/18)
  - Advisory Hospital Council, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 23/1)
  - Air Pollution, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 23/2-3)
  - Air Pollution Control Authority (incl. Metro Billings Air Quality Control), 1964-1968 (Box-folder 23/4)
  - Air Pollution Control, Advisory Council, 1968 (Box-folder 23/5)